[{
    "question": "Which is the largest mammal on earth ?",
    "choices": ["African Elephant", "Rhinoceros", "Giraffe", "Blue Whale"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
            }, {
    "question": "What species of Ant is the Anteater careful to avoid ?",
    "choices": ["Soldier Ant", "Fire Ant", "Black Bog Ant", "Red Barbed Ant"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
            }, {
    "question": "There are 2 main species of Bison, the American Bison and the Wisent. What are the Wisent commonly known as ?",
    "choices": ["Asian Bison", "European Bison", "Russian Bison", "Arctic Bison"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
            }, {
    "question": "China's endangered giant pandas subsist almost entirely on what food ?",
    "choices": ["Eucalyptus", "Hazelnuts", "Bamboo", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
            }, {
    "question": "What is a domesticated Caribou referred to as ?",
    "choices": ["Antelope", "Reindeer", "Moose", "Elk"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
            }, {
    "question": "Cheetahs are the fastest cats on earth, but what can't they do like other big cats ?",
    "choices": ["They cannot climb trees", "They cannot see very far", "They cannot roar", "They cannot hear very good"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
            }, {
    "question": "The Jarkov Mammoth is the ancestor of which of todays animals ?",
    "choices": ["Hippopotamus", "Elephant", "Rhinoceros", "Buffalo"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
            }, {
    "question": "Which big cat has the strongest bite relative to its weight ?",
    "choices": ["Tiger", "Leopard", "Jaguar", "Lion"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
            }, {
    "question": "What continent is the African Wild Dog native to ?",
    "choices": ["Asia", "Europe", "USA", "Africa"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
            }, {
    "question": "Why do wolves howl ?",
    "choices": ["To entice mates", "To confuse prey", "To communicate long distance", "All of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
        }]